rtbooster.com 2017-08-30

# Booster.DCA: Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy relates to Booster.DCA Dynamic Creative Optimization (DCO) service that our company provides to advertisers, publishers and content providers. The Policy came into affect on the 4th July 2015, and was last updated on the 4th September 2015.

Booster.DCA respects the privacy of internet users. We consider protection of consumer privacy our priority. We do not collect, process or otherwise use any personal information in Booster.DCA. We never sell or rent any personal information collected from you to any third party and will not buy or otherwise accept any personal information from any third party.

We do collect, process and aggregate anonymous Non-­Personally Identifiable Information (non-PII). This information is used to help our partners deliver relevant ads and content to consumers.

The information we collect may be disclosed to judicial or other government agencies subject to warrants, subpoenas, or other governmental orders.

 ** **

We do not intentionally collect information from persons under the age of 13.

#### **How and what we collect as non-PII data**

_A cookie, also known as an HTTP cookie, web cookie, or browser cookie, is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored in a user's web browser while the user is browsing that website. Every time the user loads the website, the browser sends the cookie back to the server to notify the website of the user's previous activity._

Like most websites in the internet our company uses cookies to enhance experience for users. For example not to show the same ad again, when it is not relevant any more. In other words, we want to make internet usage more comfortable by showing content that is interesting and relevant for the user.

Booster.DCA provides service for advertisers, publishers and content providers by using cookie targeting technique. To collect data we use “pixel tags” on 3rd party websites. This tags are image or javascript html tags that makes possible to operate with users cookies.

Most of our applications use rtbooster.com domain. Be aware, that part of our service (pixels) could be located on 3rd party websites. In this case those websites could collect and process your data as well.  
Booster.DCA may not be responsible for such 3rd party websites and their data collection practice. Although we do select partners carefully we encourage you to carefully read terms of service and privacy policies of all websites you visit especially those where you are requested to submit personal data.

#### **Information sharing**

Collected data is processed into targeting data segments and then used by advertisers, publishers and content providers to enhance users experience. Booster.DCA could share collected and processed data with partners, based on that collected information could be used for third party advertising purpose. To make it possible we only share non-PII and advertiser-agnostic data points with our partners. If you don’t want us to collect and process your data please use opt-out link. We never share advertiser-specific data with other advertisers without explicit consent from the owner of the data.

#### **Opt Out**

If you want to opt out from our service please use this opt-out link.  
It’s important to mention that you will still receive advertisements and content, but these content and advertisements will be less relevant to you. Because of technical limitations we could opt out only current browser, that’s why if you want to opt out from all devices and browsers you should repeat this procedure. If you delete all your cookies, you'll have to repeat the opt-out procedure within your respective browser.

#### **Security**

We protect collected data by storing it on secured servers with access limited to authorized personnel like system administrators and developers, so in cases of proper usage of the website no information will be accessible by 3rd party groups of people or companies except our partners described in information sharing paragraph.  
As of the date of the latest revision to this Policy we do not accept any payments on this website. Should this change our Policy will amended with relevant clauses.

#### **Policy changes**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may be updated or revised from time to time.  
In the event of a merger all data will be transferred to the new entity.  
In the event of Booster.DCA ceasing operations entirely all data will be destroyed within 60 days.  
If as a result of such events we change this Privacy Policy in ways that affect how we use your information, we will advise you of choices you may have as a result of those changes.  
We will also post a notice on our home page that this Privacy Policy has changed.

#### **Legal disclaimer**

Your use of the Website is at your own risk. Neither Booster.DCA nor any other party involved in creating, producing or delivering the Website is liable for any direct, incidental, consequential, indirect or punitive damages arising out of your access to, or use of, or browsing in the Website. This includes damages to, or arising out of computer equipment malfunction. Without limiting the foregoing, everything on the Website is provided to you "AS IS" without warranty of any kind, either expressed or implied, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties.

#### **Contact us**

**Data-Centric Alliance**  
Address: 119072, Russia, Moscow, 6/3, Bersenevskaya emb.  
Phone: 8 (800) 500 5218. E-mail: [privacy@rtbooster.com](mailto:privacy@rtbooster.com)

****
